A Guide to the Secretary of the Board of Visitors, Office Administrative Files, 1960-1985
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Secretary of the Board of Visitors, Office Administrative Files 1960-1985
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-1/2/1.871
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
For ten years from the date of creation, access to these records will be granted only under the procedures of the Virginia Freedom of Information Act (Code of Virginia -2.1-340 ff.) or with the specific permission of the Secretary of the Board. Researchers interested in obtaining access to these records should direct a request in writing to the Office of the Legal Adviser, Madison Hall, University of Virginia.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1987 August 27.
Contents List
- Memoranda to the Board of Visitors 1983 (Box 1)
- Memoranda to the Board of Visitors 1984 (Box 1)
- Memoranda to the Board of Visitors 1985 (Box 1)
- Board Meetings-Open 1979 (Box 1)
- Board Meetings-Open 1980 (Box 1)
- Board Meetings-Open 1981 (Box 1)
- Board Meetings-Open 1982 (Box 1)
- Board Meetings-Open 1983 (Box 1)
- Board Meetings-Open 1984 (Box 1)
- Assembly of Professors 1971 (Box 2)
- Confidentiality of Records 1969-1969 (Box 2)
- Fees 1969-1980 (Box 2)
- Membership Directory Correspondence 1960-1965 (Box 2)
- President's Fund 1967 (Box 2)
- Rotunda 1975-1980, 5 folders (Box 2)
- Student Council 1971-1979 (Box 2)